igoogleportal.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

* * *

_Just to clarify: **iGoogle Portal is not affiliated with or operated by Google.**_

This privacy policy sets out how igoogleportal.com uses and protects any information that you give when you use igoogleportal.com.

igoogleportal.com (here after referred as 'We' or 'Us' or 'Our') is committed to ensure that your privacy is protected. Should We ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using igoogleportal.com, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### What We collect

* * *

We collect the following information at the time of registering on www.igoogleportal.com

  * Your Name
  * Your Age
  * Birth Date
  * Contact information including Address, Email address & Mobile number

### What We do with the information We gather

* * *

We require this information in particular for the following reasons: 

  * To facilitate communication between you and the service seeker or service provider which ever case applicable to you may be and for internal record keeping.
  * We require your age to ensure that you are above 13 Years while registering on igoogleportal.com.

At times We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

### Security

* * *

We are committed to ensure that your information is secure. **_We never sell or share your personal information for any marketing or advertising agencies._**

### Cookies

* * *

We use third-party services which may use cookies to collect information about your visits to www.igoogleportal.com. by default your browser accepts cookies to be placed on your machine however it is possible for you to disable the cookies by changing your browser settings.

Back to top
